Guide to the Clippings File of the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- General Subjects, Series III
  - African-Americans in Medicine, 1925-1968, undated; 7 (Box 268)
  - Angola (Box 269)
  - Black Power, 1958-1967; 2 (Box 269)
  - Blacks in Australia (Box 269)
  - Blacks in Canada (Box 269)
  - Blacks in Great Britain (Box 269)
  - Blacks in Latin America, 6 (Box 270)
  - Blacks in Latin America (continued), 7 (Box 271)
  - Blacks in Latin America (continued), 7 (Box 272)
  - Blacks in Latin America (continued), 3 (Box 273)
  - Blacks in New Guinea (Box 274)
  - Blacks in New Zealand (Box 274)
  - Blacks in Art, 2 (Box 274)
  - Botswana (Box 274)
  - Ethiopia (Box 274)
  - Ghana, 1934-1957; 2 (Box 274)
  - Ghana (continued), 1957-1965; 6 (Box 275)
  - Harlem, New York City, 1925-1960; 8 (Box 276)
  - Harlem, New York City (continued), 1925-1960, 1925 August 8 (Box 287)
    Scope and Contents
    "The World's Largest Negro City." By Chester T. Crowell. Saturday Evening Post.
  - Harlem, New York City (continued), 1961-1972; 6 (Box 277)
  - Harlem, New York City (continued), 1972, undated; 3 (Box 278)
  - Kenya, 1948-1963; 4 (Box 278)
  - Liberia, 1910-1961; 3 (Box 279)
  - Lynching, 1893-1962; 3 (Box 279)
  - Lynching (continued), 1933-1947, undated; 4 (Box 280)
  - Nigeria, 1930-1960; 2 (Box 280)
  - Rhodesia (Box 281)
  - Riots, 1917-1967; 4 (Box 281)
  - Sierra Leone (Box 281)
  - South Africa, 1927-1961; 6 (Box 282)
  - South Africa (continued), 1962-1964, undated; 3 (Box 283)
  - Tanzania (Box 283)
  - Trade Unions - United States - African-American Membership, 1919-1949; 3 (Box 283)
  - Uganda (Box 283)
  - Watts, California (Box 283)
  - Zaire, 1926-1961; 7 (Box 284)
  - Zaire (continued), 1962-1964; 3 (Box 285)